http://www.coldsteel.com/privacy-policy

This website uses cookies to enhance your experience.
I agree
Privacy policyEffective Date: November 20, 2012This Privacy Policy (“Policy”) explains how information about you is collected, used and disclosed by Good SportsmanMarketing , LLC and its affiliates (GSM) when you access or use our Web Sites including those of its affiliates, itsmobile applications and online services (Sites), shop online or otherwise interact with us. We may supply different oradditional notices of our information practices specific to certain programs or activities.ContentsInformation We CollectOur Use of InformationInformation SharingSocial SharingSecurityYour ChoicesThird Party Advertising and UseYour California Privacy RightsChildrenChanges to this PolicyContact UsInformation We CollectWe collect information you provide directly to us. For example, we collect information when you create an online accountor profile, use the interactive areas and features of our Sites, make a purchase, sign up for contests, promotions, mailinglists and when you email, call or otherwise communicate with us. The types of information we may collect include:Transaction Information, such as your name, billing address, shipping address, phone number, email address,credit card information, and transaction history.Information We Collect When You Use Our Sites. We may also automatically collect information about you whenyou access or use the Sites, including:Log Information: We obtain information about your use of our Sites, including the type of browser you use,access times, pages viewed, you IP Address and the page you visited before navigating to our Sites.Device Information: Contents: We collect information about the computer or mobile devise you use to accessour Sites, including the hardware model, operation system and version, unique device identifiers, and mobile networkinformation.Information Collected by Cookies and other Tracking Technologies:We may use cookies, web beacons, and other tracking technologies to collect information about you and your interaction withour Sites, including information about your browsing behavior, purchase behavior, and other engagement with the Sites.We use this information in one or more of the ways described in the “Our Use of Information” section below. Mostweb browsers are set to accept cookies by default, but you can usually change your browser settings to remove orreject cookies. In additional to browser cookies, Adobe Systems Inc. may set a “Flash Cookie” on your computeror mobile devise when you view videos on our Services. To manage and disable “Flash Cookies” visit Adobe FlashPlayer security and privacy.Information We Collect from Other Sources. We may also receive personal information about you from other sourcesand combine or link that with information we have about you.Our Use of InformationWe use the information we collect about you for a variety of purposes. These include among others to:Provide and deliver products and services, process and complete transactions and send you related information, includingpurchase confirmations, invoices, updates, security alerts, recall notices and support and administrative messages.Provide, maintain, and improve the Sites;Investigate and prevent fraudulent transaction and other illegal activities;Respond to your comments and questions and provide customer service;Communicate with you about GSM and partner products, services, offers, promotions, news, and other information we thinkwill be of interest to you;Monitor and analyze trends, usage and activities;Personalize the Sites and provide advertisements, contents, or features that are targeted toward your interests; andProcess and deliver contest or sweepstakes entries and prizes.We may store and process information in the United States and/or other countries.Information SharingWe may share personal information about you outside of GSM and its affiliates, including as follows:With Third Parties who complete transactions or perform services on our behalf;We may make our postal mailing list and general shopping information available to selected companies we believe may offerproducts or services of interest to you;When you sign up for and participate in the interactive areas of our Sites, certain information about you may be displayedpublicly on our Sites and on third party Sites, such as your photos, stories, posts and other information you chooseto provide in your profile;In connection with, or during negotiations of, a corporate business transaction, such as a merger or acquisition of allor a portion of our business to another company, joint venture, corporate reorganization, insolvency or bankruptcy,financing or sale of company assets;If we have a good faith belief that disclosure is reasonably necessary to comply with any applicable law, regulation,legal process or governmental request; to enforce our agreements, policies, and terms of use; and to protect GSM,our customers or any other person from harm; andWith your consent.We may also share aggregated, non-personally identifiable information about you.Social SharingThe Sites may offer social sharing features or other integrated tools, which let you share actions you take on the Siteswith other media, and vice versa. The use of such features enables the sharing of information with your friends or thepublic, depending on the settings you establish with the third parties that provide the social sharing feature. For moreinformation about the purpose and scope of data collection and processing in connection with social sharing features,please visit the privacy policies of the third parties that provide these features.SecurityGSM takes reasonable measures, including administrative, technical, and physical safeguards, to protect information aboutyou from loss, theft, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction.Your ChoicesYour Information. You may update or correct information about you by logging into your online account or callingCustomer Service. You may also email us if you wish to deactivate your account, but note that we may retain informationabout you for legitimate business purpose or as required by law. By using our site, you consent to our Privacy Policy.Promotional Communications. You may opt out of receiving promotional emails and text messages from GSM by followingthe instructions in those communications or changing your preferences via www.gsmoutdoors.com. If you opt out of receivingpromotional communications, we may still send you non-promotional emails, such as emails about your purchases, account,or our ongoing business relations.Location Information. You also have the ability to turn location-based services on and off by adjusting thesettings of your Internet browser or mobile device, or by following the standard uninstall process and removing all GSMapplications from your mobile devices.Third Party Advertising and UseWe allow third parties to send advertisements on our behalf through the Internet and to provide analytics services. Thesethird parties may use cookies, web beacons, and other technologies to collect information about your use of the Sitesand other web sites, including your IP address, web browser, page viewed, time spent on pages, links clicked, and conversationinformation. This information may be used by GSM and these third parties to analyze and track data, determine the popularityof certain content, deliver advertising and content targeted to your interests on our Sites and other web sites, andbetter understand your online activity. This Policy does not apply to, and we are not responsible for, third party cookies,web beacons, or other tracking technologies and we encourage you to check the privacy policies of these third partiesto learn more about their privacy practices. For more information about Internet-based ads, or to opt out of the havingyour web browsing information used in this way, please visitwww.networkadvertising.org orwww.aboutads.info.We also may use a third party to “power” product reviews on our Sites. When you submit a product review, you become subjectto the terms of use and privacy policy of the third party and the reviews you submit may be posted on our Services andon third party web sites.Your California Privacy RightsCalifornia law permits residents of California to request certain details about how their information is shared with thirdparties for direct marketing purposes. However, under the law, a business is not required to provide this informationif it permits California residents to opt in to, or opt out of, this type of sharing. GSM qualifies for this alternativeoption. To opt out of having your information shared with third parties for direct marketing purposes, please callCustomer Service.ChildrenIn accordance with federal law (The Children’s online Privacy Act), we do not knowingly collect personally identifiableinformation from children under age 13 without the verifiable permission of a parent or guardian. If you are under age13, you are welcome to browse our Sites. However you are not permitted to use any of the features of our site that requirethe collection of any personally identifiable information. If we determine that we have erroneously collected a childâ€™sinformation, we will immediately undertake to delete that data from our records.Changes to this PolicyGSM reserves to the right to change this Policy from time to time. If we make changes, we will notify you by revising theEffective Date and, in some cases we may provide you with more prominent notice (such as adding a statement to our homepageor sending you an email notification). We encourage you to review the Privacy Policy section of the Sites on a regularbasis to stay informed about our information practices and the ways you can help protect your privacy.Contacting UsIf you have any questions, comments or concerns about this Policy or about our privacy practices, please call our customerservice representative at 1-877-269-8490 or send an email toCustomerService@gsmorg.com. You may also direct your privacy-related comments or questions to the following address:GSM OutdoorsAttention: Privacy Officer5250 Frye RoadIrving, TX 75061
Cold Steel Inc.5250 Frye RoadIrving, TX 75061
Sitemap
Home
Login
My account
News
Help
Basket
Subscribe to our newsletter.
Subscribe
© Copyright 2020 Cold Steel Knives. All rights reserved.
About usContact usHelpPrivacy policyDisclaimer
Loading
